The number that's
not in Google Ads
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
I met with a
high-level Google
Ads strategist
today
and the most
important number
we discussed
about these
septic clients
isn't actually
their Google Ads
We went through
two client
accounts with the
strategist from
Google
We kept coming
back to lifetime
value compared to
what it costs to
get the customer
The target is a
customer worth
about three times
what you paid
for
Once you know
what a customer
is worth over the
years or your
lifetime value
you know how much
you can afford to
pay for one
Stop judging ads
by cost per
click
Judge them by
what the
customers they
bring are worth
If you want the
simple version of
how to think
about this
comment value and
I'll send it to
you